In the temple of silence where the secrets are kept
Where sandalwood rises and the lamps never slept
They laid down five flowers on a brass gold plate
Blue lotus jasmine and a shulker mango
A blossom of fate
And the air turned sweet like a vow being sung
They began
Come it ever came softly no thunder no
With a sugar cane bow and a parrot green
Roar be string humming like him on the edge of his head five floral arrows like spring
When the soul dares to speak
Come, Eshvari, the queen of the moonlit flame
In red silk glowing, sovereign of name
Sri Chakra behind her, a geometry
Sun where desire becomes wisdom
Where to become one?
She held him like stillness holds ocean
Not a cage, not a leash, but the love inside
Not a chase, not a race
As a kingdom that blesses the
What's up, my ninjas, my ninjas?
Hey, I tried, I tried.
I tried to be as nice as possible.
I think I got some laughs from even people
that didn't like me.
I think I got some couple of laughs.
You know, we don't want to live for the lulls.
I live for the lulls.
You can laugh.
If it's a humor kind of thing, you can't,
weak person
But thank you for liking that. I know I was on Sam Ants. I'm trying to make Donald's right
I'm gonna walk to McDonald's with my phone and stuff
Alright my orders add to the basket. Okay use deal
Add a pickup order use deal
This is already in the basket. Hey, it's in the basket. I mean look at the shopping cart review and pay
Perfect. Yes, I
Love you guys though. I know I show my butt there. I don't think I have a bad butt
It's like okay, da da da da da. I'm loving it. Okay. I mean if I'm the phone now
Give me phone. I can order the fries and the the
Big Mac kind of meal. Where's my phone?
How are we doing guys?
It's okay. I know everyone's over there, but I think I was like the drawer at a peak
Hi Trix. Hi Trixie
And this is that okay, I'm gonna unplug my mic
Yeah, they did Kate they ganged up on me, you know RG was cool
Trip and sip was cool until they started saying I'm gonna teach you how to how to tie a
Slipknot to because you should die
Sam and was kind of cool
But it was even okay
Guessing I'm bad animals Rudy is 17 years old. He's an old man
You know this old man. He wouldn't put up with with that shit. He would just say I'm gonna go walk somewhere
So Rudy likes me
Three you're happy you're happy with me. I'm like Peter Peter. You're like that. Oh like that. Oh look at he likes it
That's good. Oh
Ruby you're like that
You're a little old man, right?
You know my friend my friend
Yeah, I'm gonna try to order some McDonald's. I'll take you McDonald's with me. I had to charge the phone a little bit
It's a 0% right now. So I already drink three drinks. I
Mean I had drinks. I don't even sip was gonna say I should commit suicide. That was kind of like a weird thing
I don't know Alexander was gonna strike me again
Alexander I'll just unstrike myself again. I mean it's like
But you're doing actual images of me, me.
I'm not showing your image or anything.
I'm just, I'm just, yeah.
But you want to strike me again?
You're so petty.
You can't even talk to me.
And why are you mad at me?
Because I said, are you mad at me?
I think that's what I said to her.
And then she turned against me when I said that.
Hey, Monica Foster, look up Monica Foster Tennis Court.
You can see two white Dixoner and a black Dixoner ass.
You wanna see that?
I know, I'm walking into Lion's Den, but that's not,
yeah, you didn't, yeah, you didn't see him.
You wanna see two black Dixoner butt
and a white Dixoner pussy?
Go look up Monica Foster on Pornhub.
There's Alex mayors
You didn't see that one we'll go look it up you can look it up. Yeah, you can look it up look at Monica Foster
porn hub
sir step
To stop it. I can't stop it right now because they've gone too far
He actually said oh, I can see how to tie a knot a slipknot and I want you to kill yourself. That's what he said
So tripping kick and who I let I let he's making money off of me
my streams by
By streaming a rumble and he wants to say go kill yourself. Okay?
And once I do I hope your channel is great, you know, I
Do have a good heart
It's actually good now that okay. I'm at 2% now. So yeah, here we go
But he actually did say that I'm kind of my feelings should be I he said that tonight to me
He said oh, I have a not for you the slipknot
I'm gonna show you how to tie it. I
Did show I didn't pull my boxers in my butt crack a little bit and bend over maybe
But not so good to learn but I'm not gonna use them for bad purposes like that
He didn't have to say that and he was like I'm serious, right? I
I let him use my content. He actually makes money off my content on rumble
You know the zandabita. Yeah, well, he's a little bitch, you know, he's a little bit of a bitch
You can tell he's like a closet gay
He's being facetious. Okay. Well when he says hey, I've been out for you psyche. He'll slipknot
I want you to learn this one and I want you to put yourself in it
Okay, if he doesn't make any money on rumble, it's fine. I mean Chris Casey is making it 250 a week at rumble or something
He's on my shit list now too because he didn't have to say that but
Trippin sip
You didn't tell me to tie it tie a slipknot
You didn't say I have a knot for you
Tell me strippers of it. Tell me what you said of it. I want it
I don't want to accuse you anything. Tell me what not you told me to tie and why
You don't want me to die well if you tell me about a suicide knot and you say
I'm gonna tell you how to make this exactly. You'll get the wrong idea. If I get the wrong idea, I'm sorry
You didn't say slipknot, you said let's put the video tutorial. Okay
Okay
The running knot
Is it running out of good not is that like, you know, you're trying to like, you know, run a sailboat
I know about sailboats and stuff. I
Was on action a pirate schooner when I was a senior in high school. You had a pirate schooner
But that's what you said. You didn't have any bad intention. Okay. Okay. Okay. Hey guys. I'm already we don't
I mean, I'm gonna get a big Mac large fries
I'll take you guys with me when I go the fool might die. I need to pee
But I didn't have a nice but yeah, if you admit he's like, oh, there's something in your butt. I showed it again
There's nothing my butt. My butt is looks good. My butt looks good. I'd appeal over
I'm back. You're the best part of all of it is. The best part of all it is. I'm not offended. I'm not offended. I'm not mad.
I need that.
Yeah, I'm not. Yeah. Superstition isn't going to last. I know it will last a few minutes. Someone's texting me. They're saying fake, concrete, they're saying
346 error code. That's what I'm saying. My phone is going crazy.
Um, I'm a weirdo. Yeah trip. You don't have to sit. Why did you say that to me though trip cake? You're just a chicken must kill myself
But then you told me to kill myself you said I would I would not for you to learn right
Well, you're gonna you're gonna you're gonna go to Bronzeberg and like listen to him and so I'm at 3% now
I'll wait until it's at 10% because that will give me the McDonald's a bag.
I do get the alcohol.
Bronzeberg's having fun.
Guys, I think everyone had fun.
I think I was like, I was like, let me just be funny.
Let me come with that.
I'll put my...
Oh, here.
Oh, don't hit your butthole.
I said, let me just be funny.
Let me pull my, you know, my boxers up my butt crack and bend over and stuff.
People were laughing. I mean, it's like but I don't have like I'm not like a Cyrax where I have like swars of my butt and stuff
And alcohol I'm gonna get some
We did some hard-eluminate. I don't know
My best friend in the world was black
Nor I would never call you and the n-word
Right Lenore
My friend you my best friend she's my best friend
We had her
Lenore, are you gonna let anybody hurt your poppy?
You know your poppy?
I am.
I won't, I'll be back thing.
Hey, isn't it a silky?
I'll be back, you give me a minute.
I'll just see you in a couple of minutes and do this shit.
But hey Lenore, you remember this friend?
Are you purring?
I brought a lot of straight guys out in the closet.
I know I did, I did clumsy.
Hey.
No, no, no, okay. No, you're butthole. No, no, but no butthole on stream
I don't I don't want to show mine on Samans, but I didn't because I was
Holding myself back. I
Could have and the kiss
The North's awesome you're my best friend, you know
You're purring. Oh, you like that home. They rub your back like this. Are you happy? You're happy. Are you happy?
If I was an animal abuser, do you think a cat would come up to you like that and just like you'd rub on her head?
Ever did anything mean to this cat? Ever. Lenore is awesome. Is this she?
Lenore is awesome. Maybe a spanky-spanky. Maybe a spanky-spanky.
Maybe a spanky-spanky. Oh, you're so weird little friends. Oh
Lenore. Be a lady, please. Yeah
You can't give me spanky spanky
You guys see the the you know, you know Alexander is straight to strike me again tonight
And she started this started flagging all my shorts for like having better language. I know I love you
Alexander I'm sorry, but like like in the porn industry on my show you'll fail
You know, okay, the porn industry. Okay of my show. Okay, lady
The
Oh, I love you. I love you, too.
Yeah, you're not going to go.
You're not going to get very far fucking with me.
I already dealt with Tony. Tony is worse than you.
Right. Tony tried everything.
You really tried everything.
You should have purring.
You're just purring.
I love you so much.
You know, I love you more than my life.
You know, I love you more than my life itself.
You're my best friend.
I know. I love you too. I love you too, Lenore. Lenore.
I know. We're best friends.
Oh, I mean with my nose. You put my nose.
You just bite me on the nose?
Why are you biting me on the nose? You biting me on the nose?
You're the best. You know, isn't that...
You hear some sweet purrs? Oh, yeah.
Oh, you like that when I rub on your...
Wait, we rub...we rub...necks?
Can I give you a neck?
Hey guys, I have an Aunt Biddy.
My Aunt Biddy, I went to South Carolina.
I stayed with my Aunt Biddy.
Oh, my mom is my grandma's sister.
She passed away earlier.
I love you.
How many do I need for?
For what?
In flea collars?
But the cats don't have fleas really I mean it's like because the cats are indoor outdoor cats
And so they really don't get fleas. I do comb them and I think any fleas they do have I comb out
You my friend
Just purring
But any but anything you guys if you guys I'm psyche awakens on a cash app or Venmo
If you do want to donate to the show, I know I love you, too
You're my best friend
You'd like she does love me
She loves me guys guys this cat loves me
Yeah, they're a little bit outdoors they don't need flea collars, but I do comb them and stuff and
Sometimes I do have flea medicine. I did put the medicine on my friend. I'm gonna for the medicine
The medicine is pretty expensive
It's like a hundred dollars per dose
You're we're friends hey et phone home
You're my friend I love you too
Kisses on the lips
I'm seeing people talking about it too
Because look my cats are so happy
If you ever seen a happier cat, I mean really you're just here permanently listen to this cat purr
You hear her purr?
She loves me but I met her she's a baby
You were a baby cat and you came you were my little black cat and we were best friends instantly
We best friend
We best friends instantly
We were instantly
And Lenore, have you ever betrayed me?
Have you ever heard my feelings?
Have you ever said, oh, my nails are dirty
or anything like that?
Never, never.
Nor does it care.
Are you happy, Lenore?
Lenore, just tell me if you're happy.
I just want to know if you're happy.
You're on camera.
I love you.
You know I love you?
I'm your best friend, okay?
my best friend
Not like someone like beta that's gonna like oh
I'll turn on you because you said this or that person said that no
I know I know my best friend. She's my best friend
You're getting all the other cat videos recommended you blame me well
They hear the purring you know they hear the purring
Guess I'm gonna go for a walk. I'm what percentage am I in now?
At five percent
Okay, I'm gonna order McDonald's. I'm gonna go for a walk. I'm gonna turn on the phone. I'm gonna get me
I'm gonna get a big Mac with the fries
For like seven bucks plus they already got the coffee going
We'll get two coffees. I might need to cook and then I need to get some alcohol too
And we're gonna have fun tonight guys. Okay. I love you next and next you know, you're awesome. You defended me
I don't forget people that have my back
Even if you count his bathroom was like laughing at some of the stuff I
Even appreciate that. Yeah, I mean, I don't hate anybody really. I love you, sweetheart. Look at this. You're just purring so loud
You're purring
She's happy. It's Friday. I
Didn't have a bad time. I
Love you, too
Hmm, you know, you're my baby. You're my you're you're my you're my little girl
It's my my daughter. Hey, I love you too. Oh
She's so sweet. I love you. You know, I love you
Am I ever mean am I ever ever been mad?
Well, I
Know I know
Oh, oh my nose you bit my nose. It's okay
Big Big Mac with the fries
Large fries Big Mac add the bubble order
Got it. Okay. I can't use it on that one. I need to use it on my other phone
You know guys, and I love you too, and I know it was like weird tonight. It was a weird night
Man, I have to go for a walk tonight. I'm gonna go for a walk. Okay. Let's go for a walk, Lunar, Lunar
You don't have to follow me. Lunar, you stay here. Okay
Wait, you want to go right back on me? Uh-uh
I'm gonna go right back up. I
Love you guys guys. I love you
I say bad things to some people so my feelings get hurt.
But it's like, I'm allowed to say any word.
You know what words are?
Words are what humans are allowed to use.
Every human, we all have the right to use words.
Does a word hurt anybody?
No, it's not, well, you mean kisses?
You know, I have kisses.
She's the best.
And Tricks is sitting over there.
Okay, I'm gonna take the phone with me.
Okay, let's go for a walk.
I'll be right back. How about a nice song well in the middle so can I know a oh?
We're doing some IRL. I'll be right back with the IRL
I'll play I'll play my I play a nice song in the middle
I'm stuck in the middle with you, and I don't know exactly what I should do
Oh my gosh, oh, we have a track of all men that are playing some of my show
Let's I'll put on my show my show. I think are cuz I think Arthur does the beat impression
I'm gonna see the beat impression. I'll be right back with the IRL, but look at this shit. It's pretty funny
The Arthur called in we did the beat up impressions and that Christine impressions and stuff like that. This shit is funny
Your lap he's laughing he's coughing loud because he's laughing so hard
Watch this
Huh
Oh my god
Oh, no, I thought you were addressing it to me because my name was not Matt.
Okay.
I don't know.
Can Tommy hear me.
You go to think of Tommy.
Yeah.
Tommy, I asked you, how are you doing like three times?
And you were just like, all the time.
Yeah.
Tommy, why are you being so rude, Tommy?
No, I'm not.
You know, Sam.
I got that fucking rapper vibe in the outside.
I'm trying to find my label, bro.
I'm just, I, G6, I'm just, I know, so I just not.
That stuff might it could be sensitive and I'm not going to take that fall from that trust. Yeah. I know trust me
I'm good
Oh, hold on I could dress my chat
It wasn't sensitive when she showed him on stream
Oh my god, all you want I got I could talk to my chat know that right?
I'm just saying she showed him on all her strings and that's what I know
Damn!
On all the streams that I saw, and like when chicken went over to your house, you showed them off.
Oh my gosh!
That's what I know!
It's like one of your big uh...
Can we go back to it again?
Oh my god!
You guys come on though!
This is wild! A man is a veteran in my past that I don't know. That's wild.
If you go through this again, I feel like I'm in trouble.
I need to talk to you.
You got to focus on that, Nick.
You are, but you keep bringing it back up to 2000.
Yeah, G6.
Exactly.
G6 is your fault, G6.
Oh my God, I can't talk to the chat.
Oh my God, everybody, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me.
You call me messy, but you're messy,
breaking, kicking the chat messages about it.
I see you.
Anyways, can I just say one thing?
I am sorry that I jumped on the panel thinking
that side you was on.
the panel talking about now you go personally and I just want to apologize because now I feel really
30 seconds and I hear my name and I'm like what the fuck
like he is uh Sagittarius
hey psyche you look like you're psyche you look like you're not here that's a new trip
Oh my gosh.
That's everybody on camera.
DZ.
Sorry.
That's everybody.
Man, are you going to trip?
Like the trip.
What up DZ?
I answered the question the other day.
And she said, I didn't do it.
It was setamanda.
That's your name.
I swear I didn't do that.
Now you're throwing me under the bus.
DZ.
How do you feel about Capricorn?
I want him to come up.
Right now, let me speak.
Psyche's in the chat, and I want him to come up
to explain himself on this.
Oh, there you go, Psyche.
Oh, yeah.
Crystal Ann, there you go, Psyche.
You can explain to him.
Yeah, Psyche, can you please come up
so I can ask you the question?
He's a Capricorn though, are you compatible?
Are you compatible?
Shut up!
I really wanted to resolve this with you.
This is funny.
But here he is talking about me and they're saying I'm bacon fuck.
So I just have a question.
Oh my god!
Look at it in the street.
He ain't coming up now.
Wait, what is the bell ring about now?
Ask for the link. All right, link. Oh, we're gonna link it up one-on-one. What should I do one-on-one?
You gonna handle that
Okay, one-on-one we're gonna give that one-on-one
You know when you need to tag me in, tag me in.
It's your first drill.
It's your first drill right here.
What is this?
Is it going to be a tug team match?
Troop?
No, no, one on one.
One on one.
You want that one on one?
You want that squabble?
I think I can handle myself.
All right, we dropped in later.
Yeah, he needs the link.
We're gonna get that one-on-one and Squabble beat that shot to beat it.
You guys are all fucking up.
I was going and I don't know why I'm just laughing.
Everything is funny, even from like this pause.
It's like he's on the panel, but he's coming on the panel.
Oh my gosh, I summoned Psyche.
Well, he summoned me. I don't know.
I jumped the link three times.
Is he still alive or something?
Come on, let's go.
I think your B should be with thing that is.
He was the one who talked about it.
Let's play it until 11 o'clock.
All right, we're playing.
We're gonna play the concert.
We're gonna play, yeah.
We're gonna play the concert while he,
we're gonna get on.
Well done.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, there you go.
Oh, we got him.
One on one.
Okay.
Psyche.
One on one.
Okay.
In this little clip,
I heard you say, I'm fake, I'm judgmental.
Okay, I'm walking, I'm walking, I'm sorry.
If my phone dies, I have a few percentage left.
Crystal, I have no problem with you.
I know Karen did talk to me about you and stuff like that.
Is that why you called me fake and judgmental?
Hold on.
I'm saying I'm a bad person with like this other guy
because all I,
Because you actually talked about me before I talked about to you first
You were like re streaming old streams of mine. You're talking shit about me and I wasn't even online
I wasn't trying to talk to you about you. I was like, I was man of beta
And I was thinking you were talking about beta started it. So I yeah, maybe I started it. Okay, okay guys
I'm a shit starter. I get my feelings hurt. I misunderstand things. I'm not like part of this community for like the capricorns
Okay, I didn't start that so it doesn't make me a fake or a bad judgment person because you don't know you're cool
Crystal you're totally cool. You're so cool. Okay. I know
I don't know problem with you at all. Okay. Okay, cool. That's what I just say
I like, I like you actually. I think you're like, you're pretty funny and
Oh hell no, we need cooking Christine, we need this cooking
Crystal, you're so easily manipulated, it's crazy
I already told you, like I'm not here to make friend review, I'm here for one thing, and it's just for that one person
It's okay, I know Karen is like a little bit
She's nuts
A little bit kooky sometimes
Very kooky
So Karen called you, Jill?
Yeah, that's why that sounds like that.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Cut that out.
Hold on.
What, Karen?
Karen, are you carrying your real number?
I've been talking to her for like three months.
Oh, my God.
He and Clumsy have been mentioning me.
Three months?
Yeah.
How much money she gave you?
Nothing.
Zero.
All right.
Stop lying.
Karen, donate.
Yeah
Like I don't have you know, you know, you know like Karen stocks and and harassed crystals family members
Well, I don't like that and she shouldn't and you know Karen also
We all we all have
Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, Higger, H
I don't know, you gotta say the hard-on word, come on.
Come on, stand on it.
Well, you call it Bronzeberg, right?
Come on.
That's Bronzeberg right there.
Right next to you.
That's Bronzeberg.
I have another big back-end surprise.
He says the hard-on.
You bitch, you ass nigga.
But y'all, he's got to eat.
No, no, no, you've got to be tripped.
Come on, you guys.
Let him do it.
Let him get his transaction.
Like, you know, what is it?
Just in case.
You want to get beat in there?
There you go.
Stay safe.
I'm hot right now.
It's really hot.
It's like black guys.
Then it's going to get you to say, oh, I'm hot.
No, you go.
You go.
I'm hot.
But we got risk right now.
I'm like me.
I'm strong.
No
Went off based off the parents stuff about me. So then he talked shit and then that's when I started
I didn't mean to talk shit, but you know, she was like, oh, you know, this and this and I was like, well
That sounds a little bit exaggerated
Like everything that she said last night in those five I don't even know Kate like that. I really don't I only know
I understand and Chris, I have nothing against you. I think you're like funny. I respect the Aaron Carter stuff
I mean, I was watching Aaron Carter. He's on Dr. Phil
I don't care about that stuff. That stuff is like way old, way old. I was like
This is just what I'm like coming into this thing told and stuff.
Am I falling asleep by the diet?
I don't want to.
And I got no DVR on, right?
I just don't like.
I don't know, right?
Do I?
Oh my God.
Do you?
Can you go back?
Let me look.
Ha ha ha.
All I saw.
All I saw was an air car.
Can you still turn the DVR on when you're?
Yeah, I can rewind.
I can rewind.
So pack me up.
I said it with the age ring, you two.
I got to go, I got to go, I got my phone ringed over and over again.
All right, well, good thing that's-
His phone's ringing, he said?
No, his phone's gonna die, I think.
That phone was ringing.
I thought he said it was ringing.
I thought I heard him say ringing over and over.
Yeah, Karen's calling. Karen, what up, boss?
Yeah, most likely.
Oh, probably.
Karen is calling.
You guys are all fucking out.
Stay away from the witches.
Man, we got to come.
He got to take the link back.
Damn Karen might be calling that nigga
She was like stay away from those witches in crystal and she's the one that starts all this shit. No, it's not
I'm not the one starting shit. Oh my god dragon flies. Nobody told my Eric Carter. Oh my god dragon came out of nowhere
You can come over here dragon. He hit the Whitney Houston
Yeah, he was a weirdo anyways
I think that was made with all of that stuff
That you blowing up control those DMs earlier
Well, not me. Okay psych did psych did okay psych did
You heard like I'm not a bad judgmental person. Um, I don't know who the other guy is and I don't have time for the other guy
That's a game. That's your game. I didn't hear that. I didn't hear that. I apologize. I didn't hear that
My my question was answered and I'm good now. I didn't hear that my body. I don't mean I don't be hearing psych sometimes
Oh, you need to hear him ask what I have to say.
I mentioned Eric Carter, no, I didn't, I didn't hear that.
I heard it.
He just said he has respect for him and then that's when, yeah.
It's like, that's like not as...
I love candy.
Nobody really wants to talk about that.
It's bad.
Let's move on. Yeah, let's move on. God damn.
You might have to take a two-year hiatus break like I did.
Let's move on.
Never.
Uh, I'll do it again.
God bless America on this Friday.
Bita, what the fuck will happen?
Enlist?
Yes.
One more.
Okay.
Bita.
I'm gonna have a family.
No.
Speaking of North, North Cal, North Cal.
What's he doing under the blanket?
Did you know that INX says that you hit on?
What?
I knew it!
I knew it! No kind of like big panties!
Yeah!
Even after all the jokes!
Bridget, I had that CD too when I was a kid. I had that CD too.
I give you permission to post my new artwork.
He know the big panties.
We go cook dinner, we go cook dinner.
Yeah, you gotta pay, you gotta pay.
I know Norco has hit on me before,
and I had to tell him to like pay attention to his art.
Oh my God!
He used to be like...
Damn, don't probably try to hit on the snow, buddy.
No, he's a spider.
Yeah, pack him up.
Pack down the gun.
Pack him up.
No, don't pack him up.
I won't pack him up.
That's what you know, pal.
Yeah, all right.
Next is all, like, you're kind of sticking in on me and shit.
But you're just laying out.
And I'm thinking to myself, like, nobody is hitting on you.
All right.
Thanks, buddy.
No problem.
So you know Cal hands up to you know Cal I guess that's a no-cut no-cut been around
She's such a coward. Oh, she was stopping the coward
Not gonna fight for a bunch of people that
So and I get it. Look how the people that have gone out the veterans
I respect them. I could know your answer
The veterans have done it I could never do it, you know, I
Respect them. They've given up so much. What they mostly given up is their health and their time
Something that you can never get back and I am willing not willing to lose that
You know, I am a big Trump supporter.
It's like doing another to go blankets.
You see that movement down there?
Yeah, Jason Palestine.
That makes zero sense.
Well, something that taught me to be selfish.
Yeah, things are true.
Because they will make mistakes in all time.
It's got like a really deep word to it.
You're going to have a good luck spinning.
I think right here.
It's you and me.
So I'll come back later though, I think if I fuck it, I'm out of your pocket.
Okay.
All right.
I'll be back later when I'm more awake and stuff is back stage dude, hold on 83, please
dude.
Please.
There's 83 people, bro, you got to be.
What does that mean?
I don't know what that means
You don't know what dual means
They must argue they must battle they must go to war
Right here look look this was shot to three feet. This was psych and um, I mean sake Arto was talking about earlier
Maybe I can give you some of the way
Okay. Yeah, I can use a couple hundred pounds.
And, you know, maybe with the extra fat, you can feed the cats.
That's cute 45.
Yeah, yeah, the cats.
Now, psyche, I'm,
I'm going to continue talking about you at betas. Is that okay with
Well, we can't can't really stop you
Good because we plan on sending more cinder blocks to your house. Oh my god. That was you
Did I say it was me you said we
You know entertain a shit right?
I meant her not me. I'm sorry
That was a slip. I I didn't eat it. Oh my god
That was totally her you call the police on me. No, it was she did. She put it in the Facebook group chat
I don't you haven't even gone on Facebook for like four years
Can you talking about you if you continue to exist? Oh my just existing
Because she's done a spell with
Oh my god
They're doing spells on me
Give you the heads up or should I do your trip? God, they have a baby witch. You got it on Etsy
I think you have a baby witch charge a trip being messy. I see you travel you we got an elbow in the making you heard
I see you being messy as I said to you trip respect always
Juve seven you're thank you trip for taking a link always
Maybe which set you got some crystal balls. You have maybe a really a cauldron and a
the broom and stuff. It's something similar to that. Are you in the broom gang? Is that what
the broom gang is? Which witches? We're just against you sake. That's basically it. Yeah, I know.
I actually, we're here on the Facebook group chat right now.
Yeah. Hello. Hi, I'm here. He won't beat on you now. He act like he's on the phone with
look. Yes, thank you. You're not the very nice. Why would I do this time? It's everything
You make me cry. I can't, I can't even speak right now.
I'm sorry, Vita. I'm sorry.
I need to talk back away.
It's all my fault. It's all my fault.
Okay, my fault.
I need a white claw right now.
I can't stand you anymore.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry for everything.
Well, see, he didn't want people to play this. You see, he tried to start a pot up.
You didn't do anything wrong.
You know, you talk about this and talk about that. You ignore everything about me.
Fuck you in the tattoo. Fuck you.
I know, I'm trying to get up to you.
That's what I'm trying to do.
No, it's not funny.
Fuck you, you're fake.
It's all gonna take part of it.
Indeed.
Now you're going to make one of these little bats.
Really?
Occur, occur.
Did you just call me a batch?
You're a little bat, you're my little bat.
Are you getting the tattoo?
I'm going to give it to you.
Hold on.
This thing and I will dance it out.
I think Leon is I and X.
You're going to dance?
I'm going to take it around.
How do you know?
Because they just stalked my friend.
Wait, oh my god.
Don't say that, Dan.
Just attract.
Oh my god.
I'm pretty sure that's I and X.
Hey, don't you DM me when you see stuff like that.
You heard?
Okay, yeah.
Damn.
Oh my God, INX.
Oh my God.
And I was threatened by that account, too,
saying, and Crystal, don't cry when the fuck
shit starts happening again to you.
I haven't done anything except I only had beef
with one person, so it'd be hurt.
Oh my God.
INX is oh my God.
INX, don't make me play them voicemails.
People will set me, okay, bitch?
Don't make them do it.
I'm back.
Oh!
Hey, Jamie's Cowboys.
I'm back.
I have my French fries.
I have, like, and I dropped my beer,
and so it, like, started squirting everywhere.
Where's my ex-girlfriend, guys?
Where's my ex-girlfriend?
Oh!
That's a good one.
There you go babies.
My babies.
All for you, baby.
Yeah, I love you.
Love you so much.
Okay.
Oh, I'm back.
Where's my cup?
I heard it.
Okay, babies.
Yeah.
My beer exploded on the way home.
Hold on.
Oh my gosh.
That's crazy.
What the fuck was that about?
Is that it? Where's the leak? Where's the leak?
Oh my gosh. I don't see it. Is that it?
Someone's spurting out. I think it's over here. Here it is.
Is that it? And there it is.
We're out. Oh my god, it's leaking everywhere.
There's my burger. Did he go with my burger? No, he did it. No, he did it. Oh my gosh.
Here, finish it up. Here. There we go. I finished it. Okay, it's okay, babies.
We walk over there. Oh my gosh. Oh, it's fucking cray cray. Okay, Trixie. Oh my gosh.
How are we doing guys?
Mmm, I think that is a burgers fine
No water
That's all good
I have always watered.
Boys food.
What's up guys, here, I'm with Linkup.
Someone come hang out with me.
I was a crazy walk.
You ever see me on the Sandman show?
I think it'll be too bad.
A little bit crazy.
and the cats are fine it's just it's just it's just a secret sauce
McDonald's secret sauce
cats are all good
come on get it yes
I love you so much here the water is full but
Fresh for you, my babies.
OK.
Woo.
How are you guys doing?
Leave it on my lip.
It's pretty good.
Pretty fucking good shit, actually, this shit.
I know, I have my POS, right?
We're shilling. The cats are all traumatized. Look at how traumatized the cats are.
You can see how traumatized they are.
No, you're very upset
Oh, wow, that was good
I think a little bit drunk tonight, I got a little bit upset, but you know, I'm good now
We're all good guys. Hey Michael. We're drinks drinks. You're upset. You're upset. You know drinks
We were snuggly with me for like eight hours today
I'm such a happy. It was such a happy like little beautiful beautiful cat
Well good everybody's happy
Thank you, Jamie. I'll be right with you, too. I'll wait
If I'm a cigars
You're sneezing you sneeze you sneeze
Okay, the fries are coated in hot sauce now.
Oh, here's my cigars, not cigars.
Oh, I'm all good.
Okay, how's everyone doing?
Got McDonald's tonight.
And then Trippie's starting to say the N-word
when I was having my phone on,
and McDonald's next to like eight black people.
And they're all looking at me like,
What the fuck? I mean, it was bad. It was bad. I had to turn my phone down. I was like, don't say that. It was a mess
It was it's a total mess
Absolute mess. I almost got beat up by like the whole black family was gonna get in on it. Ever seen the movie?
Yeah, I forgot what it was called. They provide me napkins. Yeah, they do
I have it somewhere around here.
I don't know.
There's somewhere around here I'm gonna have to.
My mouth will go.
The N word is funny.
I think most people can enjoy it.
I think most people can just like have a laugh at it.
It's ugly, it was, it used to be an ugly word,
like back in like the slave times,
but it's like most people, they kind of reclaimed it and
I don't know.
Only when I say it, it's a problem.
When I say it, oh, someone's offended now, right?
That's the only time they get offended when I say it.
Everyone else can say it, Bita can say it,
Sammy can say it, like a thousand.
He said it like, I think my friend
who was counting their night, he said it like 50 times
in like 10 minutes.
When I say it, I was even spelling it out
and they were still offended.
You never say I don't like to say it, but you know Jamie's another I get so mad
There's no other word that comes off my tongue so easily I
Don't I don't try not to
But we're talking about Lady Bathory and beta and in Sam-Man. It just it just comes off my tongue easily
And I'm not perfect person. I'm not a perfect person
And that song, Who Was Sank, my friend Joni introduced me to that song again, because
I'd forgotten it for quite a while, but it was like, that's what, like, I was like this,
I was like, Joni and I, we get it.
I love Joni.
I love Jamie.
I just think that it is.
I love everybody else in the chat too.
I'm not a perfect Perl, Elbchildzak, person
So many times I've said this thing before
But I intend in learning
You like the media impression?
What?
This is my media impression
I know, I need to stop giving you that
I know, I need to
I dropped this beer on the way back, but I saved most of it
I found a reason to be.
I found a reason for me to change who I used to be.
A reason to start over new.
And the reason is you.
Okay, I would play the music tonight, but all is under mayor start to strike you my channel again
She has nothing better to do with her life than to strike me
I mean this loser porn star bitch whore cunt fucking n-word woman, okay?
I'm not I mean I was trying to be nice about it, but yeah, you're gonna strike my channel at least three times four times n-word
You're an n-word porn star cunt. You've took dick sip your ass and your pussy lady, okay?
That's what I think about you
Sorry, not sorry
She wants to put me bald balding, you know
worshiping demons
Killing children and then it's like oh, I just have to oh, oh, and she's this nice lady. She's a cunt cunt whore bitch
n-word
I could say it. I would say it
Then actually she was probably sue me. So I'm just gonna say the n-word
n-word I
Know I know clouds act. I know just now she's trying to strike me again. I
Don't know Tracy. She's striking my channel. This is like going personal, right? It's getting personal
It's like fucking fucked up
I don't care if I'm involved.
I mean, I posted a picture of me today.
You can see the picture I posted.
Excuse me.
Do I have the picture still?
I don't know if I still have it.
I put this as my thumbnail.
Is it this one?
No.
How is this one?
That was one, that's when she did it with me.
Hold on.
I'll find the one on my phone.
That's me like stalking Chris Lann and Tommy James.
Is it this one?
No, that's Sweet Pea.
That's Sweet Pea's photo.
Hold on, I'll find it, hold on.
Is it this one?
That's Sweet Pea again, OK.
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
Hold on, I think I have it here.
This one?
No, this is another one. Oh, that's good times and the Kool-Aid man. Okay. Oh, that's clumsy. Yeah, is it this one?
I'm sorry. I have so many photos guys
Where's my bald photo?
No, that's Lilith, it's like a pretty picture of Lilith
The snake is biting her titty
TITT what I don't know I can't find it but I did post a picture of myself. I do it a grok and get it home grok
That's where I make some of my images grok
And I don't want us I don't want to go as low as she did but she just went low
He's trying to strike my fucking channel guys. I mean it's like she just wants to shut the channel off
It would what do you want? Don't want me to talk about you here. I found it. I found it here
Okay Z B. Okay. I got it. I got it. So guys
What I look bad
Crystal Crystal have those those dolls that are like people have miscarried to them
They have this like realistic baby dolls. Those are kind of scary, but I don't I don't know shit
My grandma was a doll maker. I don't really give shade to that
Because it's like, you know, some people like just like doll, you know, I collected these living dead dolls for a while
Let's see. Hold on. Downloads? Is this one it? Is this one it? Oh, here I am.
That's me is thing that is. How do I look?
Thing that is. How does that look?
I don't think I look bad.
I mean, it's not perfect. I mean, it's not I have like little lines on my my head and stuff, but I think it looks sexy.
Bald
You like that one or a rain I like that too can rain come up and talk to me or any talk to me
I need a friend right now. You can come talk to me. You know what these people are doing. I'm so sad rain
Come talk to me rain Jamie Gotti. Who's here? Where's every where's my friends?
You're gonna come up looking good. I'd love you to come up. I want to talk to you. Yeah, I mean Alexandra posted me
Literally, like I'm sitting there. Look at the pictures you posted of me
I'll say what she's posting of me
And with my real image and all this shit, right? It's like not like oh here's like a cartoon
Like this is a cartoon right there. Let's just consider a cartoon
Sweet that's a sweet pee, right?
Crack it on. Hey guys, let me know too because I think peps wanted me to do a reading for Zaya tonight
And I want to do it, but I'm not sure
I can like keep track of stuff if you can tell me if I'm peps or Zaya is on and I'll go over there and do a reading
I'm sorry, I'm sorry I did that. I'm sorry. I was walking to McDonald's and I just left it on
I'm sorry about that, but look what she did look what they did to me
Look what they did to me when I see what they make me look like it's like it's like if I was involved would I like
actually
Just like make it myself a mullet. What I do a ball of mullet. I mean these people are insane
Look at this. Look at this
That's a little hold on I
Know I love you Jamie is this one
look
That that's what they're doing of me and then she's striking my channel. She's using my entire image
Right? She's taking my image and then she's gonna strike me. You cunt, okay? You fucking black cunt
Okay
You're gonna do that to me and I'm gonna be racist or anything like that
I'm pissed off. You're gonna strike my channel and you're gonna do that of me and then say oh my gosh
You played a 10-second clip of my show where I'm talking about AI you cunt
Ooh
I want to say that the N word is so bad, it's just so bad.
Hey, hey Rain, how are you sweetheart?
Hey, psyche, I'm good, can you hear me?
Yeah, do I look like that Rain?
Look at what she made me look like.
Um, why are you bald?
She made me bald, she took off all my hair,
she made me eating McDonald's, the police are outside,
I say I'm Jesus.
Who did that?
Alexander Mayors, my friend.
I suppose it's wrong.
Yeah, like I hate fake people. Oh, she was so fake. She's just so fake people that just pretend to be your friend
Just to try to get something from you. I know but she was trying to get information too
She was like, oh, you know, I have a little bit of money from my you know my my my inheritance
Let me you know donate something to you
Let me pretend to be your friend get information from you and then I'll say you're a demon worshiping a child killing cult and
And then I'll strike your channel. That's what happened.
Dude, that is fucked up.
Oh my gosh.
I can't believe some people are like that. That's crazy.
I know. Well, she is crazy. You can watch Monica Foster's things on Pornhub.
She's getting gang banged by 10 white guys on the tennis court.
That's disgusting.
Right?
But I'm but I'm I have dirty nails. And so I'm a bad guy, right?
No, like for as long as I've known you like you're not like trying to provoke people like
Yeah, you might talk a little bit of shit here and there, but you know, it's harmless. I
Am harmless, but she's actually saying oh well keep away from this guy. Don't donate to him
He's where he worships Lilith and Lilith is a kills kills, you know
I mean, it's like, it's just, it's really, I can't even repeat our allegations.
They're so sick against me.
I mean, it's like.
It's fucking it's really upsetting and you see those ones you didn't even look at the worst thing
Here's the worst thing. She did she posted this picture of me. Look at this
This is the most insulting sad picture of ever seen in my life. I cannot believe that someone would make this of me
You won't believe it yourself like you like I I'm Christian and I know we have different beliefs
But I know that deep down. You're not a bad person. She did if she did look at you made me do
Who's that? Tell me James and me. I
Don't even know who that is. Well, you're lucky, but I'll show you another one. She did me and me
She's made several about Lilith and stuff. She also made this one of me
And this is this is the ultimate insult. She had beta and Sam man
Throwing me into a dumpster
On fire. Look at this. Look at this one. You're gonna be shocked people can be so
Nasty and cruel. That's that's what that's what look at this one
Where's the dumpster fire? Where'd it go? It's a runner. It's a runner somewhere. Where is that dumpster fire? I
Don't know why I didn't come up home one more one
image file
There's the dumpster fire
Look at this one
Think I have to take some down actually. I have so many pictures up. I'll just take up some down
Okay, I'm sorry, right. I'm missing you for willa, but how's the JT? I miss JT a lot
Oh, he's good. You know, he's streaming on his channel. Um, you know his gaming channel. Yeah, I don't know if you've seen it. I
Have seen this game. I've been there. I said hi. Do I'm in stuff?
But yeah, look what they did. Look at me. Look at this one would be then Sam and burning me in a dumpster
That's messed up
It says, imagine claiming to be a powerful and knowledgeable practitioner of building
to realize you're the literal sacrifice of a Jewish mysticism ritual designed to complete
the process of manifesting, live, and semi-ell into the world.
Are they trying to portray you as Jesus or something?
Like what the fuck?
No, I'm not sure.
I don't know.
I mean, I'm just it's just confusing to me. It's like they're trying to sacrifice you like you're the sacrificial lamb or something
because
There's I mean, I thought it was bed middler and like, you know
The Michael Thomas Hall from that that I think this is more evil than like whatever there
I don't know. Whatever you're trying to do. Well, look the thing is look at the image
I mean the image. I'm screaming images evil for sure. They're being burned in a fire
You like that one make my tail will fuck you man. It's offensive to me
I don't want to be burning my genitals being burned in a fire I beat it and Sam man
I mean that's that's like the ultimate insult. They don't get it. Okay. It's fine. I'll take it down
I'm gonna take you this down. I mean, it's just ridiculous
It's getting a little bit silly at this point. I mean and look I can't have a good assistant that look how good
I would look with actual a ball a ball of sense of humor a ball
We've did you make that I made that one. I made this one
Don't know. I don't like bald people. You don't like the ball people. Okay. Well, you should you should wear a wig or something
I will but I'm actually not bald. I just said I said make me bald. I
Know I
Try I try my best. I mean, I'm trying to really laugh along with it, but it's just so hard sometimes I
Get it, you know sometimes
Today too by the way, she struck my channel
Today yeah today
And then I got it taken down or the strikes taken off and she did it again today
I think on the same video actually how many strikes do you have so far?
I mean, I've had in probably 30 strikes, but I've got them all taken down
And
Now she struck your channel again. That is so petty
For like 30 seconds of her stupid show, which is talking about me
I don't know like I'm not gonna talk bad about beat up, but from my experience
I was on her mayor's not be the be the be the be the stroke me once I forgive her
It was I was on her mayor's that shook me all these times
Oh, well, I don't even know Alexandra Mayer, so I can't say no to her.
She's a porn star that turned into like the expert of the IRL community.
She became my friend, we went to dinner once.
She donated a lot of money to me, had over 10 readings to me, sent me breakfast, sent me gifts.
And then when I asked her if she was turning against me she turned against me and now she's been saying that I'm doing
Magical rituals for the Mexican cartel over the Mexican cartel
They don't even know who you are I know they don't but well clumsy knows who I am
I don't know if he's in the cartel or not, but I mean, but I'm not doing that you do magic for him
He didn't give you a dime
Clumsy if you want me to I mean I can but then I'm speaking from for all Mexicans
And no the cartel does not know who psyche is. No. Well, are you sure? Can you look at you have the files?
Yeah, I have the files. There's a rain knows rain would know
Yeah, El Mencho El Mencho. He was my uncle
Rest in peace
So guys I have friends in high in the high places
I've reigned. She has the whole database on the last time
some more today and the MS-13.
She knows everything about it.
Was my name found in there once, Reign?
What happened? Sorry, I didn't hear you.
Was my name found in the MS-13 files?
Nope, not at all.
Not one time. One time.
Do you have the access to the Epstein where they found the Epstein files?
No, not the Epstein files fuck that shit. No, not in the Epstein file. I was I have never been to Epstein Island
I did file for a visa there. It was denied. I
So I was never there. I wanted to get a massage
But but actually from Jeffrey Epstein not from anybody underage. I want it actually you
He was ugly as fuck. Well, he kind of looks like I wanted him
I think it's Anthony Bourdain. He would have cooked me a nice meal
Did you see those gums on that guy? What the fuck? He had large gums. Hey, how about the x-file?
Have you you see me in the x-files?
No, no, I don't even know what that is
she's like the librarian of
Underworld and she has not seen any of it. It's all it's all lies
Yeah, they call me the librarian
But you're a sexy librarian you were those of the glasses and then you're like, yeah, she's a sexy librarian
Is Jade? I'm sorry. Is he around?
He's in the other room. Do you do you want to speak with him? Can I just for a minute? Yeah, give me one second
Thank you so much. I love you
Love you too psyche. Yeah, you're awesome. I love this. I love this couple that guys
This is a power couple of the year. I think they have all the files
I want to talk to JC. I haven't heard it for a while. I want to hear what it's up to
He's playing his video games, it's okay
You guys see, I put my underwear, I put my boxers in my butt crack tonight, and I pretended I was a Sumo wrestler.
Here he is.
What is this?
Where have you been?
I've been around.
You just abandoned me? You know what I've been going through?
Well, what's been going on with you?
Alexander Mayors, Bita, Samann. I said the N word several times.
Oh, so you just had like a full crash out then you just yeah, I did I did and I could have used you by my side
Well, it's like
You know, I just been in my a I don't know. I didn't even do games. Yeah, you know, I'm just chillin
Relaxing I'm actually doing it right now. Yeah. Well, I know I know it's a bunch of bullshit in this world
But you know what I like JT. I like if you I want to see the wolf man
Call me at f-a-g-g-o-t a couple times in my chat once in a while. I miss you. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, I'll come back and I'll definitely call you
I know I know I know you and Rain are having the time of your lives
But hey, I'm over here. I'm struggling
Struggling what's the struggle? What's going on?
well beta
Sam and Alexander Mayer's now now I'm part of a a cult
I mean, it was supposed to be ironic that I called myself a cult, but now I'm actually
called a cult.
It hurt my feelings that I didn't see you.
I wanted to watch you play.
I want to be in your Grand Theft Auto game.
And you said, you said I was rejected from the game.
Well, Grand Theft Auto 6 hasn't come out yet, but when it does, we can, we can play together.
No problem.
Okay.
Well, I'm going to let, I'll let you go.
I know you're busy playing your game and you have a hot girlfriend and stuff.
But I want to say, you know, JT, I loved you, you know, not in a gay way, but just in a homie kind of way.
But I do have a boyfriend now. His name is Squidward.
He's real, right? He's not like a...
No, I saw Six Vagina. I saw...
Oh, that was, yeah, that was really...
You saw Six Vagina too? Hey, but you know what? I want to say, no matter if you're here or not or whatever...
Hey, you're a really cool couple. I wish you the best and
You guys have fun. Okay, and you know, don't worry about me. I'll be okay, too
You know my friend Danny stranger got shot in the chest three times, too
He was on YouTube and stuff if you know who was he was a cool guy
But yeah, there's something going on that you haven't seen I miss you guys and just stop by what maybe if you can stop
By like once every couple months and just say hi to me
Don't forget about me. Okay. No, I haven't forgotten about you
I just did you know I got had to get away from all that shit. I know I know I need to get away from it too
But I can't I can't because I'm in it
But but I need a friendly face once in a while and I miss you. Okay, and you and rain
Can I be your flower girl at your wedding? Yeah, absolutely. You're the you could be the best man
You'll be the flower you'll be all of that. Thank you. All those things. I love you. I love you
And I want to bother you you go back to your game and and you know great
You know, right psyche no more vaginas on your stream and you know, this is my vagina
I don't want to see it. Yeah, don't let signal show us vagina. Yes. Oh, yes
He actually showed his vagina a few times
and everyone has seen it, and that's the end of that.
Hey, JT, I love you, and you're always a good friend,
and thanks for putting up with my bullshit, and so.
All right, Swaggy, take care of yourself, buddy.
He's a cool guy.
Anyone else wanna come up?
Come on up, guys, I'm gonna put this to the link one more time.
He is a cool guy. He's a cool guy. Hey, you're you know, you're he's lucky man
I say he has you and I say you're lucky. You're both lucky, you know
Thank you, psyche. You're welcome
And he said I can be the flower girl and the best man at your wedding
You could even be the the maid of honor if you wanted to eat of honor to oh my gosh
That's a lot of outfits, but I'll okay. I'm down for a costume change
Yeah, if you ever, you know, feel like you want to put on, you know, like a fancy dress you can
Well, I do. Do you have a outfit I can borrow?
Yeah, but it's gonna be pink
That's fine. That's fine
That's fine. Hey, erase a rain. Yes
Yo quiero erase a rain. Oh
Yo también te quiero, Saiki. Yeah
Hey, 2S, La Bamba.
La Bamba.
Have you seen that movie?
Um and everyone laughed oh
I remember that yeah
Yeah, the speedo on I've done it before too. Hey. Hey. Hey, I'm a legend. Hey, don't forget psyche
Don't forget that
Psychi wasn't trying to get like all this attention for himself. I was trying to make everyone else just laugh
Yeah, I remember you did that at Vader stream, too. I did on Vader stream. Oh Vader like it a lot
You better didn't pass away, did he?
No, he's still he's still a long but I had a friend named Danny stranger you can look up Danny stranger
He looked like kid rock. I was like his he was on all the time recently
You know kid rock when you look at kid rock buddy kid rock side cute in a way
But Danny's not I wrote for like being had 1.2 million views on it on a stream of his for getting fired at Walmart
But then he always had like three or four people in the stream. I said like 40 people were streaming so happy
I got a bunch of, a bunch of memberships to his channel.
Danny got shot in the chest three times,
a couple of weeks ago at a gas station when he went on,
and it was on the stream.
You could hear the gunshots and stuff.
And so prayers to him.
But yeah, I mean, just like shit has just happened
and people only like sometimes care or know that it's like,
my heart hurts right now for the shit that's happened.
Hey, team Kisco, but look at Danny's stranger.
So now he's really cute.
He's passed away now he got he got shot several times at a gas station. Oh, you can hear on the stream
but I
Actually want to play
You can you can say if you want to I'm gonna play he was like getting his these um these bottles ready because he
We he did one high and push-ups. He and this was he did these two shots of like of
Stuff but you can see how cute he was. He didn't like he did like kid rock
He was also really nice to me. He danced for me in his underwear one time
Me and me and mod then he started charging me money once I owed it enough to buy him a truck
I started coming around until he forgot about that, but
If you can watch this one little thing, and I want you to go cuddle your boyfriend and
like, you know, you know, just remember, like life is like short.
Sometimes you don't have our, I'll be here or anybody will be here, but, um,
Kid Rock is trash though.
No, maybe he is, but, and maybe Danny was a little bit, a little bit white trash
and stuff like that, but he was actually a good heart of person.
Um,
Where is it? I don't know, I don't see it on my, I'm in a private, I'm in a homeless area.
Whoever that, whoever that M45 person you had last time on the panel, like yeah, they need their devices checked.
That's my boyfriend Squidward.
That's Squidward?
Yeah, it's my boyfriend named Squidward, and he actually converted to a homosexuality because he fell in love with me.
Well, he looks like he does the sex offender shuffle.
Well, I don't like that about him
That stuff as up it
He's almost like mustache and stuff
But yes, that weird 80s mustache
When I say to him, I'm gonna squeeze your cheeks
He gets a little giggle and that's just cute to me
Do you like when he has a little giggle about that?
But here let me see me. Let me see my videos. Where's the Danny stranger? I don't
Here is okay. Do you want to watch the Danny stranger video real quick before you go? Yeah, what up Clowns?
Okay, you can see how cute he was he was very cute and he this was when he was preparing
Some some some shot
He was gonna he's gonna fucking
Do these shots here is right here. Here you go. It's really cute. There he is right there
And I'll play this little quick
This is a song I wrote for him and I didn't actually get to play this for him before he passed away
And he loved it and I got we passed away
I didn't know that I was in the chest in the gas station a couple weeks ago
But here is Danny stranger guys and I'm gonna smile at this
Look at you
Then it's stranger walking in like a county fair star
Looking so cute got that kid rock guitar bar
I'm actin' normally and sure, okay
But my brain's yellin' open, I made your way
He did one little dance and my soul said,
Find out I'm losin' my dignity one beat at a time
I don't hit him up much, I keep it tight
Cause he's got that charm that can wreck my night
One smile on hate and I'm already sure
He'll talk me into somethin' expensive, love
Danny Stranger, yo!
You're trouble you're cute
He got that I might be a problem grand
Like he's selling sunshine with a side of sand
He laughs, I fold my wallet, get scared
I'm tryna play cool, but I'm deeply unprepared
I'm not sayin' I'm obsessed
Just molly the range like who needs self-respect
When the vibes is strange
I keep my distance, I do my best
But he pops in my head like a bad text
he says we should hang i'm like maybe soon then i'll hide in my house like a raccoon
danish stranger your trouble your cutie tag i want to buy your underwear and your socks and a
pack you dance for me once now i'm down bad facts but i'm keeping it casual i'm losing my tracks
and oh we ain't gay so don't make it weird i'm just out here spiraling crystal clear i don't
Who would talk me into buying him a whole dang truck?
And I don't even have a bike to...
I'm a responsible adult allegedly
But that man says, babe, in my brain, go spend money
I'm not his bank, I'm not his plan
I'm just a humble fan with a morally questionable stance
If he blinks twice, I'm making poor choices
voices Danny stranger you're trouble you're a cute attack I wanna buy your underwear and
your socks in a pack you dance for me once now I'm down bad facts but I'm keeping it
casual while I'm losing my track so no he ain't gay so don't make it weird I'm just
out here spiraling crystal clear I don't talk to him that much cause I know what he'll
do
I don't even have a bite, dude.
Danny Stranger.
Please stop being adorable.
My finances can't take it.
He was a really sweet guy.
Really nice.
Well, rest in peace and let's pour one out for Danny Boy.
Yeah, we love Danny boy, right? I love you rain. Thanks for being on the show. I
Don't know him, but I wish yeah, like you know
You can see I wish his loved ones the best and you know
That's a good aura about him. I can't you like you can see he has like that
Just a good guy, right?
Yeah, he seemed like a cool dude. He was a cool dude in his channel stuff
He had a 1.2 million people
Watch one of his videos
And so we went viral.
They always had three or four people in his chat
and a couple, like probably three weeks ago,
probably 21 days.
I told everyone in my chat to go to his.
He had 40 people in his chat and he was so happy.
And then like a week later, he was gone.
But yeah.
Oh, I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
And and rain, thank you for being my friend. You know, I know I'm not the best person in the world, right?
And I'm not I've probably I mean nobody is really but you know
As long as we're there for each other even though I'm not around much, you know, I'm still here
And if you ever need me rain you ever need me for error or if she if she needs for new reason
I'm just I'm like I'm here. That's why I'm still here. I'm here for you guys and
Thank You psyche same to you. We're here for you, and I love you. Thank you
Love you too, psyche, but I'm gonna jump off
One more thing
You give a hug to your boyfriend for me not in a gay way. Just give a hug to your boyfriend and
or your fiance or your
husband or whatever he is and
I'm gonna give a big hug to you and know that I love you guys, okay?
Yeah, I will ever if you ever need me for anything. I'll be here for you. Okay?
So, so are we psyche we're here for you to thank you. I love you so much. Okay. Love you too psyche
Take care of yourself and talk to you later. Thank you. I love you. Okay. Bye. Bye
She's really awesome. She's really awesome guys and so is so is JD so is Goddy so is even Vader
And I and I probably got in my thong for Gator to or Vader or whatever his name is
But I really do wish everyone the best. I can't believe Alexander would do that to me again
She's gonna continue to try to strike my channel take my channel down
She's gonna be the villain of my story a little bit, but you know what?
We have to be the villain in your story Alexandra, I'm already the villain in your story. I
Am dumb really
Okay, I
Mean I just wanted them to like have fun and so if I'm dumb, it's okay. I'll send the stream this stuff
If you see I'm dumb and stuff, but it's okay
But I love you still and I'm sorry Sam and I wouldn't have been anybody I'm gonna use a word and stuff
My feelings get hurt sometimes and then there's a lot people just laughing me and stuff. No one's to help me and stuff
It's okay
I'm gonna end the stream. Have a good night guys